<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure Functions on Jonathan&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://jmezach.github.io/tags/azure-functions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure Functions on Jonathan&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 09:14:51 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jmezach.github.io/tags/azure-functions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Pull Request bot with Azure Functions - Part 2 - How it works</title>
      <link>https://jmezach.github.io/post/building-a-pull-request-bot-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 09:14:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmezach.github.io/post/building-a-pull-request-bot-part2/</guid>
      <description>This is the second post in my series on building a pull request bot using Azure Functions. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read my first post I strongly recommend doing so before diving into this post. Remember that this series is a part of the Applied Cloud Stories initiative.
 Part 1: Introduction Part 2: How it works Part 3: Operating it  In this post I&amp;rsquo;ll dive into the details of how the bot actually works, from receiving notifications from Azure DevOps to managing state and posting comments back to the pull request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Pull Request bot with Azure Functions - Part 1 - Introduction</title>
      <link>https://jmezach.github.io/post/building-a-pull-request-bot-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 13:49:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmezach.github.io/post/building-a-pull-request-bot-part1/</guid>
      <description>About 2,5 years ago I was talking to my fellow team members about some of their challenges. At the time we had recently switched from TFS Version Control (TFVC) to Git, which obviously introduced quite a few changes in the way we worked. For example, we introduced pull requests as a mandatory step in the development flow in order to increase awareness and code quality. However, we found that some things that would need to happen for every pull request weren&amp;rsquo;t being done (or not done properly) which weren&amp;rsquo;t always caught by reviewers either.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>